[Characters, behaviors, places, organizations,
professions, or events shown in the series
are entirely fictional,
solely for the purpose of entertainment,
with no intention to instruct
or promote any kind of behavior;
viewer discretion is advised]
[Phop Phra, Tak]
♫At this hour, I shall solemnly solicit♫
♫The sacred master
to whom I am deeply indebted♫
♫To protect and to shield my spirit♫
♫With the holy mantra♫
♫Incantation, and sorcery
arching over the sky♫
♫There dwell ethereal blessings,
veiled in protection, to guard the mortal wight♫
Master Bulan.
You can't be in here.
The master is in the middle of a ritual.
I am a cop.
I need to speak with her now.
I have something important
to discuss with you.
♫Along with ghostly spirits
hounding relentlessly,♫
♫May the maras be ravaged
and perish completely♫
♫Vindictive spirits, tyrannical psyches,♫
♫Meant to betray, slaughter, and invade,♫
♫Were any souls to brush
against my karmic soulmate,♫
♫They shall bury the thought
of returning to their realm♫
♫With incantation and virtue as shield,♫
♫At my feet,
they shall surrender and kneel,♫
♫Chanting, "Sadhu," of their own will♫
[A day earlier]
Peem,
how many of these have you had?
You planning to stay up all night or what?
If I fall asleep
and Krating suddenly shows up,
what are you gonna do?
It wasn't easy
getting a lead on his hideout, Phu.
Never in a million years
will I let him slip through my fingers.
Peem,
I'm serious.
Ever since what happened with Pat,
you've been working yourself
to the bone every day.
I think you need to take a break.
I know.
I tried!
But you know what?
I haven't slept soundly since.
I'm afraid that
if I fall asleep,
something bad will happen again.
Peem,
you do know that Pat's death
wasn't your fault, right?
Next month would've been Pat's birthday.
I was going to buy this for her.
Pat came to me in a dream once, Peem.
It was as though...
she was coming to collect
the present I'd promised to buy her.
And in your dream...
what was she like?
Just the same.
She was wearing
her favorite blue floral shirt
you bought her.
She loved that shirt, Peem.
Even after she wore it until it tore,
she still had it mended.
She refused to throw it away.
I want to see her, too.
Then, on her birthday next month,
let's go see her together.
I'll give her this present.
Mm,
let's do that.
I have a present for her, too.
Phu.
We've spotted the target.
He's entering the warehouse.
All units, stand by.
Await further instructions.
Peem!
Stop!
Don't move!
Drop your weapon!
Put your hands up!
Don't move!
Sit!!
Sarge, take it from here.
Peem!
Take care of this.
Stop!
You piece of shit, I told you to stop!
Peem, what are you doing?
We've got the guy.
The suspect was shot once in the torso.
Send for an ambulance.
Four officers were injured
during the arrest.
Fucking shoot!!
You are...
so fucking annoying, officer.
Don't even think
you'll get away from me.
What the fuck did I ever do to you
to make you fixate on me
like a dog with a bone?
It's your little sister, huh?
No wonder...
when that wench was on my bed...
Shut the fuck up, you fucking bastard!
Your sister really took after you.
Hey!
Stop!
I said stop!
You piece of shit!
(Incanting)
Your gun jammed, officer?
Your brother's not, though.
Phu...
Phu.
Phu!
Phu...
Then, on her birthday next month,
let's go see her together.
Let's do that.
I want to see her, too.
Family of the injured patient,
please wait outside.
[Emergency Room]
I have a present for her, too.
Peem.
Mom...
Dad, I'm sorry.
I have something important
to discuss with you.
What is it?
Anyone who comes here
comes with a troubled soul.
You must wait your turn.
If you cannot wait, then leave.
Sure.
I'll wait in the car, then.
What are you doing?
The sanctum is closed.
Then why did you tell me to wait?
I wasn't gonna wait for hours on end
just for you to tell me
that the sanctum is closed.
Okay.
Let me formally introduce myself.
I am
Lieutenant Phitcha Ruechakun,
a detective from Bangkok.
You can call me Peem or...
What do you want?
Bullets.
I need bullets
that can stop invulnerable criminals
with impenetrable skin,
the kind who pratice black magic like you do.
I do not practice black magic.
There is nothing I can do, Lieutenant.
There's nothing you can do,
or do you just not care to help?
How about this?
The fee you received today,
I'm happy to double it
in exchange for making those bullets.
Leave
before you find yourself in affliction.
So?
When people said
your father was such a benevolent man,
it was all a lie, wasn't it?
And everything being fabricated here
is just a scam to exploit people's faith.
I myself must question
whether you are here
in search of justice,
or merely...
to have me aid you in killing.
I'm not an officer
who would kill someone outside the law.
I'm here
to uphold justice!
You dare play with faith,
yet you have none yourself.
What in all realms...
could possibly come to your rescue?
So what do I have to do
to get you to help me?
Just say it!
I still have faith in goodness,
and anything auspicious
should aid those who think and do good.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Should you be determined
to find answers to this matter,
stay the night here
at my sanctum.
For?
What for?
If you're not going to help,
there's no reason for me to stay.
If you'll excuse me.
If you do not...
come before me tonight,
do not expect...
a peaceful slumber.
Next month would've been Pat's birthday.
I was going to buy this for her.
The doctor said...
the surgery went well,
and nothing looked concerning.
They will keep him
overnight for observation
and probably transfer him
to a recovery room.
Peem.
What you've witnessed
is called sorcery.
[Invulnerability Yantra]
Sorcery...
What do you mean, Dad?
Back then,
I didn't believe
such things were real myself
until...
I witnessed it with my own eyes.
Back when I first joined the force,
I was assigned to capture
a criminal in a robbery-murder case.
Turns out...
the guy knew sorcery
and had an Invulnerability Yantra
tattooed on him,
making him impervious
to any blades or bullets.
My boss
had to summon a master
from the North to capture him.
(Incanting)
May it be ravaged,
may it be ruined,
may it be blighted
by the power of Namo Buddhaya.
Do use them
to uphold justice, as is your duty.
[How to make consecrated bullets]
So...
where is this master you're talking about?
How can I get in touch with him or...
meet him?
That master passed away many years ago,
but he had a daughter
to whom he passed down his sacred arts.
If you still want to capture Krating,
you have to go see
Master In's daughter.
Master In's daughter...
Who is she?
Master Bulan.
[Master Bulan]
If you do not...
come before me tonight,
do not expect...
a peaceful slumber.
Mommy,
I have returned to pray before bed,
as I promised you.
Good.
The merit you diligently cultivate
is never in vain.
When it is time,
you will be born in a better realm.
I am not going anywhere.
I will stay here with you.
Anyway...
the person you invited to stay the night,
who is she?
She is someone Master said
I would eventually cross paths with.
Then why did you
make her sleep in the sanctum, Mommy?
It is much more comfortable here.
Because she will soon face danger.
If I agree to stay the night here,
you will help me with the bullets, right?
Let us see if you make it through tonight,
officer.
I'd better not find out
you opened the sanctum
just to scam money out of people.
I'll make sure to get you
nice and settled elsewhere.
Who is that?
I asked, who is that?
Who?!
Grandfather would not allow me in, Mommy.
Not even to teach her a lesson.
I could not touch her.
This voice...
It is something that closely follows her.
Return to where you came from.
If you refuse to listen when I ask nicely,
I shall make sure you are never born again.
Te cha su me.
Om, may the sacred fire deity manifest.
Aggi aggam.
I shall wake the kalpa-destroying fire.
Namo Buddhaya.
♫Along with ghostly spirits
hounding relentlessly,♫
♫May the maras be ravaged
and perish completely♫
♫Vindictive spirits, tyrannical psyches,♫
♫Meant to betray, slaughter, and invade,♫
♫Were any souls to brush
against my karmic soulmate,♫
♫They shall bury the thought
of returning to their realm♫
I shall later dedicate my merits to you.
Where on earth is she?
Lieutenant, what is it
you are doing at my home?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Hey.
Hey!
What about the bullets you promised?
Hey, you!
Once you're done giving alms,
we have to talk about the bullets.
Will you stand there,
or will you join me in giving alms here?
I humbly invite you, Venerable Sir.
Now, pour the water
and receive the blessings.
(Chanting a blessing)
Lieutenant,
come make a water offering
for your karmic enemy.
Dedicate part of your merits
to those who are
still trapped in the karmic bond.
That will ease her suffering.
(Chanting a blessing)
May you be happy.
May your wishes be fulfilled.
May you be blessed.
Where do I pour this?
"Pichapat Ruechakun."
That's Pat's full name.
My sister.
She passed away last year.
If the person you talked about is her,
please just tell me
how she's doing.
I'd also like to know
if she's doing fine right now,
because ever since
what happened that day,
I've never seen her,
never felt her,
never...
even dreamed of her.
Come on.
Let's go home.
What still lingers in my memory
is nothing but the scenes
of what happened to Pat.
Pat,
I forgot my phone.
I'll be back in a sec.
Pat...
was raped by those bastards.
They recorded videos to blackmail her,
forcing her to become their slave
and satisfy their lust.
In the end...
she couldn't handle it.
Pat...
what are you doing?
Pat!
From that moment on,
I've never been able to sleep soundly,
because I'm scared
that if, one day, I fall asleep...
I'll lose my loved ones once again.
Your younger sister
is not filled with joy,
yet neither is she as troubled
as she was when she was still alive.
How do you know that?
My little brother and I
were chasing down the guy
who did it to Pat so he could be punished.
But as my brother and I
were about to close in on him,
my brother was injured
and is now in critical condition.
I know what you want,
but it is best to give up.
If you meddle with vileness,
you will only put yourself in danger,
just as you were haunted by those ghosts,
until you could find no peace.
What do you mean by that?
I need not tell you,
yet you know too well what I mean.
If you will not think of your own life,
then think of your late sister.
Consider how she could ever find happiness.
Ghost this,
ghost that.
The more I hear this,
the more I have to see it through.
Do you have any idea
how many innocent people out there,
apart from my little sister
and my little brother,
have been harmed by those guys?!
Regardless of what you think,
those innocent people
deserve justice.
I have to go home with the bullets,
no matter what it takes.
Dad,
could you have me
transferred to Phop Phra?
Could you do it right now?
Thank you, Dad.
They were born with the charm of metta.
Master Bulan.
They have a mark
in an auspicious position on their face.
Stubborn by nature,
never one to yield to anyone's objections.
That...
is your karmic soulmate.
Stay here, my beautiful daughter.
Do not leave them.
One day...
they will come to you.
I'll go ahead and introduce her.
This is Police Lieutenant Phitcha Ruechakun.
She's a detective from Bangkok.
You can call me
"Peem."
I will be temporarily stationed here
to investigate a human trafficking case.
I'm not here only to help the victims,
but I'm here...
to eradicate the ones responsible,
no matter where they might be hiding.
This is the desk
for our beautiful lieutenant.
Peace and quiet,
but not private.
You don't have to call me
"Beautiful lieutenant."
Just "Lieutenant Peem" is fine.
Copy.
You came here
to see me?
I made you breakfast,
but you left in such haste
without eating it.
So I have prepared
lunch for you in a tiffin.
I do not know what food you favor,
so I brought everything I had made.
Sarge, why did you pass the dessert
between your legs?
I've already told you
that no one can be trusted here.
There are both magic and the dark arts.
Sis!
Someone wants you
to check on your daughter at school.
They're saying that
she's possessed!
By the sacred power of Namo Buddhaya.
What is this, Sarge?
It seems she's possessed;
otherwise, Master
wouldn't have been summoned here.
- Excuse me.
- Lieutenant! Lieutenant!
(Incanting)
Stop!
I have never minded
that you do not believe in it,
but do not interrupt my ritual.
What's this master of yours usually like?
This lady... she's the real one.
She's the best in all of Phop Phra.
When afflictions come your way,
even I cannot come to your rescue.
Prove it to me, then.
I'd also love to know
if you could really banish ghosts
if they were real.
♫It's not that I don't feel it♫
♫It's not that I'm cold-hearted♫
♫For the love you've given♫
♫It's because it feels too good to be true,♫
♫So much so that I doubt if it's true♫
♫If it's smoke and mirrors,
a dream that lingers♫
♫Deeply swayed by love,
all while shaken with dread,♫
♫Scared that it's not love
after all in the end♫
♫What if, between us,♫
♫It's nothing but a perfect illusion,♫
♫Nothing short of deception?♫
♫What I've kept hidden for ages,♫
♫Do you know how painful it is♫
♫To keep my heart locked away in a cage?♫
♫Can you so gently give me some time,♫
♫For me to ponder what's on my mind?♫
♫I would hate to be wavering
when love binds♫
♫Deeply swayed by love,♫
♫all while shaken with dread,♫
♫Scared that it's not love
after all in the end♫
♫What if, between us,♫
♫It's nothing but a perfect illusion,♫
♫Nothing short of deception?♫
♫What I've kept hidden for ages,♫
♫Do you know how painful it is♫
♫To keep my heart locked away in a cage?♫
♫Tell me it's not an illusion
you beautifully created♫
♫Don't let my heart suffer
and ache inside this cage♫
♫I would do anything just to escape♫
♫What if, between us,♫
♫It's nothing but a perfect illusion,♫
♫Nothing short of deception?♫
♫What I've kept hidden for ages,♫
♫Do you know how painful it is♫
♫To keep my heart locked away in a cage?♫
♫I don't want to lock my heart away♫
♫I wish you'd know one day♫